Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
[soldiers shouting]
[soldiers groaning]
Aah!
[truck drives away outside]
[sound of swords clanging]
[men in movie shouting]
[man] Hoo! Hyah!
[man] Hooyah!
[man] Wah!
[woman accompanied
by big band singing in Chinese]
[door bell rings]
What's going on. Hop?
[Hop] Oh. you back again?
Oh. sick!
Find good one?
Yeah. Ten Tigers of Kwangtung.
This is gold.
Oh!
Bride with White Hair.
Chinese. no subtitles.
Hey. Hop. do you have
any early Shaw Brothers?
There's a guy who does Leopard style...
[Hop] Leopard style. Dragon style...
fly through air. fight on water.
Crouching Tiger. Spanking Monkey.
[chuckling] I know you.
Another white boy
who wants to know kung-fu.
Kick the ass.
Get the girls.
[chuckling]
Only storage back here.
Where did you get this?
It was here...
when my grandfather opened this shop...
hundred years ago.
He waited for a man
to come to pick it up...
return to rightful owner.
Man never came.
My father take over the shop.
Waited. too. Long time.
Now me.
That's a Northern Temple-style Bo staff.
Same kind the 13 monks used
to save the Tang Emperor.
I've seen it before.
That exact one.
I've had dreams about it.
You know why?
You watch too much Hong Kong Phooey.
Come.
Come on.
I give you five awesome Bruce Lee movie...
for very sick price.
You're the man. Hop.
[girl] Jason!
Hey. What's up?
Not much. Just. you know. cruisin'.
You been down to Chinatown.
What's up with that?
Oh. [laughs]
Kung-fu.
Are you serious?
I'm not supposed to talk about it.
not under the kung-fu Code.
Hey. look.
The new kid's makin'
time with the hoodsies.
J-boy. you still riding
this loser cruiser?
You need to get a motor for this shit.
What we got here?
Just some bootlegs. no big deal.
"Enter the Dragon"?
"The Bride with White Hair"?
Yeah. that's actually very good.
- Oh!
- Ow! Punk.
[second girl] Come on. let him go.
Yeah. don't. He knows kung-fu.
What?
You think you're Chinese?
You hangin' out with
them Chinks in C-town?
What's up with you? Let's see some. man.
Come on. Come on.
Let's see some kung-fu. huh?
Kung-fu master. Huh? Huh?
Want some Tae Kwon Do. huh?
[groaning]
[boy] Yo. Lupo.
He's hangin' out with that
old Chink cashes checks.
You in tight with the old man?
[Lupo] Just shut up and do it!
It's late. man. He's probably gone home.
He's not here. Let's just go.
- [door opens]
- [Hop] Who's there?
Ah! Kung-fu boy.
You back for more good-price movie?
I told you. best deal in Chinatown.
Come in.
[baseball announcer on television]
[Hop] Want some tea?
Red Sox game is on.
Yankees winning. Very bad.
Who's with you?
Friend?
Where you keep the cash?
I said. where do you keep the cash?
- Please...
- Come on. old man!
[sound of boys ransacking store]
Stay here!
[boy] Hey.
Found your Xbox.
[Hop gasping]
Hop!
Jesus. Lupo!
What the hell. man? You shot him!
Take it.
Must return to rightful owner.
Run.
You didn't see that. yo.
You didn't see that!
[Lupo] Come here. you little shit!
Lupo. come on. man! Just don't...
- You didn't see nothing!
- [boy] Calm down. Lupo.
[second boy] Hey. chill. man.
[third boy] Put the gun down.
Maybe I pulled the trigger.
but we're all in this together!
But this little cockroach.
he ain't one of us!
[Jason gasps]
[screaming]
[gasp]
[oriental music]
[children laughing]
[speaking Chinese]
[cattle lowing]
[children speaking Chinese]
[Jason] Excuse me.
I don't know where I am.
I don't... I don't know how I got here.
I remember falling.
[speaking Chinese]
[dogs barking]
Hmm?
[horse neighing]
[dogs barking]
[tense music]
[man] Aah!
[soldier shouting in Chinese]
[woman screaming]
[man shouting in Chinese]
[woman shouting in Chinese]
- Aah!
- [woman screams]
[shouting in Chinese]
Whoa! Aah!
[dramatic music]
[soldier shouting in Chinese]
Whoa!
[soldiers shouting in Chinese]
[man on donkey humming]
[soldier shouting in Chinese]
[donkey braying]
[groaning]
[soldiers shouting in Chinese]
- [speaking Chinese]
- What? This?
You want this?
[soldier shouting in Chinese]
[speaking Chinese]
Aah!
[grunting] [soldiers shouting]
[groaning]
[speaking Chinese]
I don't know what you're saying.
I can't understand you!
That's because you're not listening!
[footsteps] Behind you!
Aah!
Hyah!
[traditional Chinese music playing]
[men shouting]
[Jason] I don't know where I am...
or how I got here.
and who those guys were
that wanted to kill me.
But whatever you did back there was sick.
No. Drunken fist.
Secret kung-fu of the South.
I'm Lu Yan. traveling scholar.
What land do you come from. monk?
I'm not a monk.
I'm Jason.
Jason Tripitikas. from South Boston.
Is this a dream?
No.
Where you came from is the dream...
through the gate of no gate.
Is that like a wormhole or something?
No. It means
you are either a Zen Master...
or you carry something very special.
This?
It was in a pawn shop.
waiting for a man to pick it up
and return it to its rightful owner.
What?
It's long been foretold
that a seeker will come
to return the staff and end
the reign of the Jade Warlord.
Return the staff to who?
The Monkey King.
Born of a stone
on the mountain of fruit and flowers.
With his weapon in hand.
-his Chi became like fire.
-[shouting]
his stick fighting like magic.
He defied the order of the land...
but the Jade Army could not defeat him.
[Monkey King] Ooh!
[soldier screaming]
Hee hee hee hee!
[soldiers shouting]
- Aah!
[Lu] The Monkey King crushed
every soldier sent to stop him.
With his magical staff. he was unbeatable.
Word of his disobedience
traveled deep within the Forbidden Kingdom
to the Five Elements Mountain.
land of the immortals.
Once every 500 years.
The Jade Emperor hosts the Peach Banquet.
It is here. the Heavenly Ministers gather
to celebrate their longevity
and drink the Elixir of Immortality.
One sip of this heavenly brew
will give everlasting life.
free from mortal suffering and desire.
[Monkey King laughing]
[Lu] Into the banquet.
the Monkey King crashed. uninvited.
[Monkey King] Whoo!
[Lu] The Jade Emperor was
enchanted by the Monkey King.
But the Jade Warlord was not amused.
As Master of the Army.
The Warlord demanded
the Monkey King bow down to him.
[laughing]
[soldiers shouting]
He's a bit unrefined. that's all.
Give the naughty monkey
a title and let him go.
[Lu] Satisfied all was well
in heaven and earth.
The Supremely High Emperor
left to begin his 500 years meditation.
leaving the Jade Warlord
in charge by Mandate of Heaven.
But rather than obey
the Jade Emperor's command.
the Warlord challenged
the Monkey King to a duel.
High atop Five Elements Mountain
in the Warlord's palace.
- [drums beating]
- the battle of immortals was fought
To prove once and for all
whose skills were supreme.
[drums grow louder]
Yah!
[both giggling]
Hmph!
[laughs]
[rumbling]
Huh!
Hwah!
Oh!
[tense music builds]
[spears clanging against staff]
[giggling]
Most excellent stick fighting. Sun Wukong.
But without your weapon. you're
nothing but a lowly hermit!
Hee!
No more weapons. no more Chi magic.
Fist against fist.
[Lu] The Monkey King was too trusting
and believed the Warlord's words.
laying down his magic weapon.
[clang]
Hwah!
[Lu] Realizing he'd been tricked.
the Monkey King cast the staff
out into the Middle Kingdom.
Hmm...
martial art is based on deception...
my friend.
[drum reverberates]
[Lu] Being immortal.
the Monkey King could not be killed.
only trapped in stone.
where he waits for the seeker
from the prophesy
to return to him his great
weapon and finally free him.
That's what I heard. anyway.
[Chinese lute playing in background]
Long time ago.
How long has he been imprisoned?
Five hundred years.
give or take a few decades.
They say when the Monkey King is free.
the Jade Emperor will return.
How do I get home?
You must return the staff
to Five Elements Mountain.
You must free the Monkey King.
I can't free the Monkey King.
I gotta get home.
Innkeeper! More wine.
Jeez. don't you think
you've had one too many?
Wine is my inspiration.
In some parts. I am known as the poet.
Gambei.
In other parts. I am known as the beggar.
[speaking Chinese]
What do we do now?
How good is your kung-fu?
Ah!
He who speaks does not know.
He who knows does not speak.
Surely. you are masterful.
[tense music]
- Where did you get that weapon?
- It's a fake.
You can find anything these days
on the Silk road.
- Out of way. old fool.
- Huh?
Hand it over.
[playing]
Hand over the weapon... or die.
[soldiers groaning]
[patrons screaming]
Go!
Whoa!
Whoa! Oh!
Aah! Oh!
[soldiers groaning]
[soldier] Hyah!
[dramatic music]
[Jason] Aah!
[groaning]
[Jason gasping]
Lu. help!
[soldiers shouting]
[Jason screaming]
[Lu groaning]
Yaah!
Protect yourself!
What?
[Jason shouting]
Yah! Yah!
[clang] Ohh!
Ayee!
[Jason] Whoa!
[groaning]
[shouting]
Whoa!
Hyah!
[officer shouting command in Chinese]
[soldiers yell]
Let's go!
[Jason] Aah!
Oh! Ohhh!
[Jason] Where are you going?
- Jump!
- I don't think so!
Don't think! Just do!
[shouting]
[screaming]
[soldiers shouting]
[Lu] Come on!
Aah!
- Ohh!
- Aah!
[Lu screaming]
[groaning]
Ah! Thank you!
[officer shouting in Chinese]
Oh! Such skills. child!
Are you from Northern Mountains?
She is Golden Sparrow. from the South.
Yah! Yah!
[dramatic music continues]
[soldiers shouting]
[screaming]
Aah! [horse whinnying]
[Jason] You really saved
our lives back there.
I don't know what we would have done
if you hadn't come along.
She does not think the drunken immortal
needed his life saved.
You're immortal?
What do you run from. child?
Bounty hunters trying to stop her
from reaching the Five Elements Mountain.
I suggest you keep riding west
and only stop to water your horses.
You're not coming?
The journey to Five Elements Mountain
crosses barrens and deserts.
Unspeakable dangers.
Worst of all. no wine.
His Elixir.
Every immortal has one.
I'm very sorry.
Without wine. I would perish.
You must understand this.
No. You must understand this.
This is insane!
- You wish to get home?
- Yes.
Then listen well!
If you die here.
you'll be found dead
in the world you left behind.
Do you understand?
[melancholy music plays]
My jug is getting low.
I must say goodbye. Bye-bye.
Lu.
Wait!
Let him go.
You are the one
to return the staff. not him.
How good is your kung-fu?
He's got no kung-fu.
None!
[Jason] Lu. wait!
Teach me.
Teach me to fight!
[grunting]
[Lu] Swing soft. cut hard!
At the same time!
He's terrible.
I've been your weed-whacker
for two days now
while you sit on your horse
like the King of England.
When are you gonna teach me kung-fu?
You want to learn kung-fu?
Yeah.
I teach you kung-fu.
- Aah!
- That's called strike.
Tomorrow. I'll teach you block.
Let's go.
[Lu] Swing soft. cut hard.
[Jason groaning]
[gentle music]
You think you'll teach me
the no shadow kick?
Oh. and the Buddha Palm technique?
There's a guy in Virtual Fighter 2
that does the Buddha Palm technique.
Thanks. Lu.
And he does the. uh...
the Iron Elbow...
And he does the One-Fingered Death Touch.
The cup's full.
Stop! It's full.
Exactly.
How can you fill your cup if already full?
How can you learn kung-fu?
You already know so much.
No Shadow Kick. Buddha Palm!
Empty your cup.
Hopeless.
It is hopeless.
[playing]
It is said that music...
Is a bridge between earth and heaven.
It's beautiful.
It belonged to her mother.
[thunder rolls]
[dramatic music]
[thunder]
[grunting]
[thunder claps]
[gasp. panting]
Lu Yan?
Lu Yan!
[shouts] Lu Yan!
Sparrow!
[tense music builds]
[groaning]
[Jason whimpering]
Aah!
- [Golden Sparrow] Are you all right?
- [Lu] Jason. what happened?
He took it! The staff!
The Jade Warlord has sent a bounty hunter.
We are doomed.
[crow caws]
[cawing]
That's his horse.
He must be inside.
Why would he take refuge in a temple?
[Lu] That's what I intend to find out.
Wait with the horses.
[peaceful music plays]
Ah! Good to get off my feet.
Long day.
So. where are you from?
Shandong Province?
You look like the Shandong Province type.
You come here often?
That staff doesn't belong to you.
You have to give it to me.
or somebody might get hurt.
[grunting]
Yah!
[dramatic music]
[grunts]
[strains]
[sipping]
What kind of monk are you. huh?
Stealing from travelers.
Ah! A silent one. I see.
Or deaf.
I'm speaking to you. monk!
Hmm?
[wind blows]
[Lu groans]
Hey!
[groaning]
Ugh!
[dramatic music]
[music intensifies]
[groaning]
Praying Mantis. Very good...
for catching bugs.
But not tigers!
[tiger roars]
[roars]
[groans]
[burping]
Aah!
You tried to steal the staff
for the Warlord!
No. fool!
I'm on a mission to find
the seeker of the staff.
[gentle music]
You found him.
[speaking Chinese]
Ah!
[chuckles]
[laughing]
[Jason] How long have you been
searching for the staff?
[Silent Monk] As long as I can remember.
[speaking Chinese]
Aah!
[quivering]
Jason. go deeper!
Must taste bitter before sweet.
Horse stance. Grow roots.
Horse stance.
Very good... for taking a dump.
Hey!
Enough from you!
He's my student. not yours!
Two tigers cannot live
on the same mountain.
Two masters cannot teach the same student!
Ma Bu!
If he is really to learn the kung-fu.
he must develop speed.
accuracy. and power.
Hey! I know that.
It's the way of the intercepting fist.
Bruce Lee?
I will punch. You block.
Ready?
Ohh!
What did I teach you about the Snake?
Now you punch me.
[groans]
See?
Again. You punch him again.
Snake!
[choking]
He's not ready for Snake.
Perhaps Eagle.
Crane! Crane!
Okay?
[Jason grunting and groaning]
Aah!
Ow! Ow! Ow!
Aah! Oh!
Stop!
I've had enough!
No more!
No more silent riddles!
And no more empty cups!
[grunts]
First. you show respect to your teachers!
So. what about the two tigers
on one mountain?
We can kill each other when it's over.
Aah ha ha!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Ohh!
[Jason groaning]
[Lu] Kung-fu.
Hard work over time to accomplish skill.
[Jason groaning]
Aah! Aah!
[Lu] A painter can have kung-fu.
[grunting] Or the butcher who cuts meat
every day with such skill
his knife never touches bone.
[groaning]
[Silent Monk] Learn the form.
but seek the formless.
Hear the soundless.
Learn it all. then forget it all.
Learn the way. then find your own way.
[Lu] The musician can have kung-fu.
or the poet who paints pictures with words
and makes emperors weep.
This. too. is kung-fu.
[Silent Monk]
But do not name it. my friend.
for it is like water.
Nothing is softer than water.
yet it can overcome rock.
It does not fight.
It flows around the opponent.
[Lu] Formless. nameless.
the true master dwells within.
Only you can free him.
[epic music]
[music ends]
[gentle music]
[flies buzzing]
[ropes creaking]
[Silent Monk] Behold the tyranny
of the Warlord.
[Golden Sparrow] He must be stopped.
He must be killed for his crimes
and his head put on a post.
But we must not feel hatred
towards him. or he wins.
If he speaks of compassion for this devil.
he should go back to his temple and pray.
Our mission is not one of peace.
Go back to your mother and father.
You are but a child.
They are dead.
[Golden Sparrow] And she's not a child.
Not anymore.
Her father...
was a government official
who opposed the Warlord.
[soaring melancholy music]
And so. to set an example.
the Warlord dispatched
his troops into the night.
[sound of soldiers marching]
Legion upon legion poured out
of the Five Elements Mountain
into the lowlands of the Middle Kingdom.
[people screaming]
Screams of innocent people
hung in the night air.
When it was over. charred ruins
were all that remained.
That. and a lonely child. hidden
in the well by her mother...
ruthlessly murdered by an arrow...
from the Warlord's bow.
[crying]
When she reaches the Warlord's palace...
She will not offer him forgiveness...
monk.
She will offer him...
this...
a Jade dart that can kill an immortal.
Long has she practiced.
Vengeance has a way
of rebounding upon oneself.
Huh.
Master of Sensitivity.
[speaking Chinese]
[horse whinnying]
[panting]
Damn.
This desert is hot.
This is not a desert.
That is the desert!
[Lu] I Hope you know where you're going!
Crazy monk.
Oh!
[light heartfelt music]
[grandiose music soars]
[wind howling]
A monk on a mission.
And where does he lead us?
Across a desert to nowhere.
We're not gonna make it. are we?
And even if we do. we still
have to face the Jade Army.
What if I can't handle it?
What if I freeze?
Don't forget to breathe.
[wind howls]
[stillness after the storm]
If we don't find water soon.
we will perish.
Perhaps a Taoist immortal can make rain.
If he truly is a Taoist immortal.
[breathes heavily]
[gagging]
[speaking quietly in Chinese]
You are an insult to the name of Buddha!
Blasphemy!
Look!
I lead you to the mountain!
Out there!
[soaring music]
[grunting]
[Chinese lute playing]
Can you see them...
in the clouds?
A two-headed lion.
Right there.
See?
Yeah. I see.
See that one?
Right there. coming up behind it?
Like a wave?
Looks like the Green Monster.
Green Monster?
You mean dragon.
No. I mean Fenway Park.
They call the left field fence
the Green Monster.
It's true.
It does kind of look like
a dragon. though. doesn't it?
Have you family back
in this land you come from?
My mother.
Father?
Never knew him.
Do you ever long for him?
Wonder who he was?
Maybe the only thing
I've ever been good at...
pretending that I don't.
She is sorry.
[Ni Chang] How romantic.
[Ni Chang] Men will tell you
what you want to hear. Sparrow.
But in the end. they will
leave you with nothing.
You survived the River of Sand.
Impressive.
And you. boy...
so far from home.
I can ensure your safe return.
Just bring the weapon forward.
I don't think so.
Why do you want the staff?
When I deliver the lost weapon.
the Jade Warlord shall grant me
the Elixir of Immortality.
An orphan girl. a lost traveler.
an old drunk. and a monk who has failed
at the same task for half his life.
[scoffs]
Misfits following a misfit
in hopes of rescuing... a misfit.
Oh!
[dramatic music]
[grunts]
[whip cracks] Aah!
[whip snaps]
Kill them.
[soldiers shouting]
[dramatic music continues]
Aah!
[screaming]
- Aah!
[grunting]
Wah!
Oh!
[soldiers shouting]
[whip snaps]
[Lu] Hyah!
Lu! You okay?
Just thirsty.
Lu!
[grunting]
It's okay. He's immortal. right?
I mean. he is. right?
Wine. He needs his wine!
There is nothing we can do.
What are you saying?
We have to do something!
[goats bleating]
[epic music]
[monks shouting]
[Abbot] I'm afraid the wound is too deep.
He will not survive it.
[Jason] He needs wine.
He's one of the eight immortals.
Wine is his Elixir. Please.
[Abbot] We will send a walking monk.
[Lu] Don't you have a running monk?
When I was your age...
I was a scholar-warrior in training.
My arrow was good. So. too. my kung-fu.
So I was chosen to take
the civil examinations.
To pass would place me...
in the very short line
of scholar immortals.
I failed.
You're not an immortal?
If one does not attach himself
to people and desires...
never shall his heart be broken.
But then...
does he ever truly live?
I would rather die a mortal...
who has cared about someone...
than a man free
from his own death.
I don't want to lose you.
Forget about me.
[Abbot] There is only one
Elixir of Immortality.
It is the Emperor's mix of Jade.
Cinnabar. and Salts of Mercury.
It is forever stored in
the realm of the Jade Palace...
high in the Jade firmament.
rarely touched by mortals.
To reach it. one must take the north road
and cross the border
of heaven and earth...
only to face the Jade Army.
I'm sorry.
There is no other way.
Yes. there is.
In two nights. there should be no moon.
We can take the south side
of the fourth peak
under cover of darkness.
- We have to go now.
- No!
But he's going to die!
We go now. we all die.
There is more at stake. an entire kingdom.
Your passage home.
We will advance in two nights.
when the moon has ceased.
So be it!
[thunder rumbling in the distance]
When she met you...
long ago in a tea house...
you were a lost boy and frightened.
Not the kind
she would stand and fight with.
[gentle music]
[gentle music intensifies]
[music crescendos]
You've made a most excellent judgment.
The seeker from the prophecy.
Not quite what I expected.
[Jason] A man is dying
back on Song Mountain.
I need the Elixir.
And why should I give it to you?
Because I brought you the staff.
The life of your friend
for the power to rule a kingdom?
A most reasonable offer.
This man. a good friend?
And a good teacher.
The man who honors
his teacher honors himself.
However. there is a bit of a problem
with your request.
You see...
I've promised the Elixir to someone else.
But she didn't bring you the staff. I did.
The boy has a point.
My liege. you made a promise.
There is but one way
to resolve such matters.
A martial challenge... to the death.
With pleasure.
[tense music]
[apprehensive music]
The Elixir of Immortality.
The prize goes to the winner.
[edgy fraught music]
[music stops abruptly]
[chuckles]
[fraught music continues]
Yah!
[groaning]
Aah!
No!
[staff clatters]
[grunting]
Ahh!
[groaning]
[Jason shouts]
[grunting]
Enough!
[Jade Warlord] The seeker
from the prophecy.
I find that quite amusing.
Did you really think. even for a minute.
you stood a chance?
I didn't think so.
[shouting in the distance]
[grunting]
- Aah!
[shouting]
[exciting epic music]
She will kill you. witch!
Not if I kill you first. orphan bitch!
[soldiers shouting]
Yah!
[music continues]
[dramatic music]
[panting and groaning]
[groaning]
Aah!
[soldiers shouting]
[shouting resumes]
Aaah!
[Jason] Yaah!
[shouting]
[shouts]
Yah!
[gentle mystical music]
Gambei!
[laughing]
[epic music]
Remember what I taught you!
[groans]
[gasp]
Yaah!
Aah!
The statue!
[groaning]
Use the staff!
Waah!
Aah!
[energy booms]
[gentle epic music]
[groaning]
Aah!
[Ni Chang screams]
[heavenly music soars]
[panting]
[gentle music]
[wind blows]
My turn!
[shouting]
[intense fast paced music]
Yaah!
[shouting]
Aah!
Hoo!
[Monkey King giggling]
- Hyah!
- Hoo!
[shrieking]
[Ni Chang screaming]
[groaning]
[screaming]
[gasping]
[Golden Sparrow] My lord.
Who are you?
The youngest daughter
of a family you murdered.
Come drink with me.
[groaning]
[music ends]
No!
Aah!
Sparrow!
Sparrow.
Come on.
Come on. You're going to be okay.
[gentle music]
[intense music] [weapons clank]
[groaning]
[piercing sound]
[hissing noise]
[groaning]
[screaming]
[silence]
[soft music]
Jade Warlord?
He's dead.
I...
I thank you.
[soft music continues]
[soldiers and monks chanting]
[officer shouting command]
[chanting stops]
[soft heartfelt music]
Is there anything you can do?
Her destiny was written by her own hand.
I am sorry.
[soft heartfelt music continues]
[birds twitter]
[ethereal music]
Traveler...
you have come far.
through the gate of no gate
to fulfill the prophecy of the mortals.
What do you desire. please?
I just want to go home.
Ah.
Very well.
It is said master and student
Walk the path side-by-side.
They share their destiny
until their paths go separate ways.
I'll never forget you.
I guess that's what being
immortal truly means.
You freed me. traveler.
Now go free yourself.
[blowing]
[siren in the distance]
[traffic noise]
[dogs barking]
[groaning]
[gasp]
Aah!
So what's it gonna be?
You gonna shut up?
[groaning]
[coughing]
Listen. pissant!
I ain't gonna ask you again!
Oh!
[Jason groaning]
Come on. maggot. get up! Come on!
Huh?
You want some more?
Huh? Come on.
[epic music swells]
[groaning]
We don't have to do this.
Huh!
[music crescendos]
[groaning]
[music fades]
[female paramedic] Take it easy. sir.
You're gonna be fine.
[Jason] Hop! Hop!
How's he doin'?
It missed his heart. He'll live.
Of course I'll live.
I'm immortal.
Did you return the staff
to rightful owner?
I did.
You're the man.
Two. three. lift.
[siren]
Is he gonna be all right?
Looks like it.
I saw what happened.
I work across the street.
You were very brave.
- See ya.
- Yeah.
Absolutely.
[Lu] And so the legend is told
that the Monkey King
began his journey west
in search of truth.
while the traveler returned to his world
to walk the path of the warrior
and find his own truth.
As one tale ends...
So another begins.
[end credit music]
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm